Risley, Robert, Papers /4154
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Committee on Government, Industrial and Educational Relations, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Training Opportunities Projects (TOPS), 1970 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- ASTD Executive Bd. Mtg. New Orleans - Oct. 29-31, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- ASTD-Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Task Force on Curriculum in Higher Education, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- William Nourse Honorary Dinner, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- ASTD Bd. Mtg. Sept. 30- Oct. 2 1970 Lake Bluff, Illinois (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Cooperman, Harriet T.A., 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Crawford, Colleen 498, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Dandridge, Ann M, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Professor Robert E. Risley: Dandridge, Millicent/ Final Copy Dissertation, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- De Angelo, Charles M.S. Candidate, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- "Third Class Cities with Highest Total Grant Moneys, Per Capita Income over $100, and Three or More Sources of Grant Moneys" and Related Paper (Box 20, Folder 6)
- De Angelo, Charles- 499 COE Spring '77 (Part 2), 1977 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Debona, Elyse- NYC- Fall 1981 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Diamond, Tamra Fall 1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- DiVincenzo, Tom- ILR 498 Fall 1981- Lynchburg, VA (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Ehrlich, David- ILR 498 Fall 1981- DC (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Ehlers, Kristin- Student Advisee Info, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Eilers, Susan- ILR 499- Fall 1982 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Erickson, Diane M.S., 1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Evans, Ellen- 499 Spring 1977 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Student Recommendations, 1971-1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Acerrio, Stephanie, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Alves, Paget, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Ames, Nancy, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Anderson, Jon T., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Arthur, Patrick, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Baiz, Hetty, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Barrett, Edward J. (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Bassi, Laurie (Box 20, Folder 24)
- Beebe, Beatrice J., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Becker, Larry, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Becker, Jonathan (Box 20, Folder 27)
- Belmont, Kathlyn, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 28)
- Berg, Astrid (Box 20, Folder 29)
- Berg, Meredith (Box 20, Folder 30)
- Berlin, Edward, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 31)
- Biener, Steven, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 32)
- Bierman, Leonard, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Billig, Jacob B., 1976-1980 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- Binstock, Stuart, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 35)
- Bisom, Susan L. (Box 20, Folder 36)
- Blackwood, Claudette, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 37)
- Blakely, John, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 38)
- Borkan, Leonard, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 39)
- Braff, Lynn (Box 20, Folder 40)
- Brenner, Andrew, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 41)
- Breslin, Jerome, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 42)
- Brooks, Andrea, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 43)
- Brossman, Mark, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 44)
- Burrell, Dean L. (Box 20, Folder 45)
- Butler, Walter J., 1975 (Box 20, Folder 46)
- Caldeia, Vicky- DC- Fall '82, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 47)
- Cambridge, Joseph M. (Box 20, Folder 48)
- Caporiccio, Andy (Box 20, Folder 49)
- Carbone, Lawrence (Larry) (Box 20, Folder 50)
- Caton, Thomas J., 1982 (Box 20, Folder 51)
- Cohen, Bruce, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 52)
- Carniol, Rhonda, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 53)
- Casey, Kevin, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 54)
- Carson, Valerie, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 55)
- Chernuchin, Cindy, 1979-1981 (Box 20, Folder 56)
- Collins, Bruce (re Employment Walter Butler), 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 57)
- Collyer, Richard A., 1979 (Box 20, Folder 58)
- Contaldi, Linda, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 59)
- Cooperman, Harriet, 1975-1978 (Box 20, Folder 60)
- Curran, Frank R., 1986-1987 (Box 20, Folder 61)
- Cusack, Heather, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Laitamaki, Sinikka E. (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Landgraf, Paul- Owego NY- Spring '81, Fall '82, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Leland, Rick, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Levine, Katherine, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Levine, Linda, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Liebowitz, Jonathan S., 1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Livoti, Leta A., 1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- LoBosco, John, 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Lopez, George, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Medina, Lucrecia, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Lustig, Richard, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Lyon C., General, 1978-1979 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Markavitch, George (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Marks, Lynn, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Masiowski, Michele- Albany- Spring '82, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- McGarry, Lynn, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- McCarthy, Nancy P., 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- McDonough, James B. (Box 21, Folder 18)
- McDonough, Peter- Semester in DC, Spring '80, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- McGraw, Daniel, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- McGuire, Mary A., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- McGuy, Nancy (Box 21, Folder 22)
- McClellan, Michael, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Merzer, Edie, 1978-1988 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Migdal, Renee, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Miller, Margaret, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Mills, Patricia, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Moran, Debbie (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Moscarella, Christopher, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Moss, Peter, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Mott, Larry (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Musicus, Josephine (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Murphy, Stacia, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Myers, Brian, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Nematz, Diane B. (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Nichols, Sharon E., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- O' Leary, John Michael (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Otis, Clyde, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Ossip, Michael, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Pally, Marcia (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Pados, Virginia (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Parlett, Robert, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Pargament, Jeffrey, 1980-1984 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Parrott, Thomas W. (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Paspalas, Andrew G. (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Pearlstein, Lisa C. (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Pierson, Jennifer, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Pisciotta, Christopher P, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Plotsky, Ina, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Popkin, Gregg, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Porges, Sandra- Internship Credit, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Powers, Chris- Spring 1982, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Powell, Patricia (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Powers, Christopher (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Proper, Lynda (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Quickenton, Tamar, 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Rieflin, William, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- Risley, Robert, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- Risley, Tom, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Rivera, Ramon E. (Box 21, Folder 60)
- Roberts, Lillian re Carl Smith Admission to IC, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Rodgers, Patricia E. (Box 21, Folder 62)
- Roland, Mary K. (Box 21, Folder 63)
- Ross, Alan, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- Roth, Andrew- Albany- Spring 82, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- Rubinstein, Mitchell, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 66)
- Ruggiano, Lorraine, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 67)
- Salman, Amy, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 68)
- Samilow, Sherri M. (Box 21, Folder 69)
- Schlafstein, Yvonne, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- Scelfo, John (Box 21, Folder 71)
- Schaffran, Andrew, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 72)
- Schmertz, Gail, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 73)
- Schuman, Barbara, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 74)
- Schwalback, Nancy M. (Box 21, Folder 75)
- Seager, Karlyn T., 1980 (Box 21, Folder 76)
- Sears, David L., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 77)
- Segerstro, Lynn M. (Box 21, Folder 78)
- Sekas, Maria, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 79)
- Shapiro, Randi Meryl (Box 21, Folder 80)
- Sheenan, Kathleen- Albany- Spring 82, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 81)
- Silverstein, Deborah, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 82)
- Zanghi, Joseph Anthony (Box 21, Folder 83)
- Zellner, Barbara A. (Box 21, Folder 84)
- Ziffrin, Linda, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 85)
- Zitwer, Mary, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 86)
- Simon, David, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 87)
- Sinko, George (Box 21, Folder 88)
- Sirowatka, Jean (Box 21, Folder 89)
- Sisti, Thomas- 5144 No Campus, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 90)
- Skala, Frederick A, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 91)
- Slamm, Marie Margaret, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 92)
- Poch, Joel M., 1971 (Box 21, Folder 93)
- Schneider, Mary- Fall 1980- Wash (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Sebastian, Raphael- Spring '87, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Sekas, M.- Fall 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Sheehan, Kathleen- Spring 82- Albany (NYS Senate), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Shelly, Patricia 499, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Shenker, Cynthia, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Shinney, Janet- Spring 84 ILR 498- R.R., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Silverstein, Steve, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Smith, Paul Artell- M.S.- '85, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Sovocool, Daniel- Spring 1981- Washington (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Spinner, Steven- Spring 1981- Albany (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Spokane, Stephen- Spring 82, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Stamer, Cindy- Spring 81, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Sterthous, Denise- Owego, NY- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Stoecker, Nora M.S., 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Sauve, Karen L. Spring 1986 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Hone, Kathleen Spring 1983 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Turley, Thomas, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Turula, Michael (B&PA) ILR 499- Fall 1978 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Urban, Randi- Spring 83- 499, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Van Vleet, Wayne- ILR499, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Warner, Amy- IL 498, Spring 79, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Weinbaum, Michael- 499 Spring 1977 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Weinberg, Lisa- Washington- Spring 81, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Weingarten, Mark- Fall 1980- Wash (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Weingarten, Rhonda- Semester in Albany, Spring 1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Weiss, Heidi, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Weiss, Stephen: Outline and "Labor's Role in Community Service Activity, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Weiss, Stephen, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Westgate, Daniel- Florida- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Wilkens, Christine- Spring 82- VA, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Wolf, Bill- Spring 1981- Washington (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Wolter, Anita- ILR 499, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Woodward, George- ILR 499, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Zee, Teddy- 3 Credits- Spring 79, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Zenitz, Paula- 498, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Zitwer, Mary- 499 Fall 1977 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Ewald, Robert- NY- Fall 83, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Faugnan, Una- 499, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Feiner, Joe- 499- Spring 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Flack, Jill, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Forst, Robin I., 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Friedlieb, Jane- ILR 499, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Gabor, Marc- 499, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Gelfond, William- 499- Fall 1977 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Gitlin, Bruce- Spring 77, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Glassman, Andy- Spring 82- Albany (NYS Senate), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Goldenberg, Brynn- Fall 83, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Gochman, Karen Sue- ILR 498- Spring 1981 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Hale, Robert- Seminar in Albany- Spring 80, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Hewitt, Kelli- Fall 89, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Horowitz, Gary- Spring 77, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Hardigan, James, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Hauselt, Denise- 498, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Hayward, Louise- Advisee, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Henis, Russell- Washington D.C.- Fall 1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Henry, Danroy- ILR 499, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Hernandez, Israel- Fall 87, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Hochman, Brett- Spring 1981- Albany (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Isbell, Billie Jean- MS HumEc, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Kaufman, Gabrielle- 499- Fall 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Kelly, Margaret- NY Senate- Spring 83, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Kessin, Eric- Semester in Albany- Spring 80, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Kidd, Jean- Fall 86, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Kingsley, Adam- Spring 86, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Kirschner, Kenneth- 499- Spring 75, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Klein, Joyce- Spring 82- Albany (NYS Senate), 1982 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Klosk, Craig- Spring 81- Albany, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Kruse, Tom- Spring 87, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Klosk, Craig B., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Kuhn, Robert- MILR- Fall 1981 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Kurlander, Steven- 498, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Kwong, Grace- Semester in NYC- Spring 80, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- ILR 499 Misc., 1973 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Laine, Brian- Fall 1979- NYC- 499 (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Landgraf, Paul- Owego N.Y. (IBM)- Fall 81, Spring 82, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 39)
- LaRaia, Teresa- Spring 87, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Lavigne, Cheryl- ILR 499- Spring 81, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Lester, David- Spring 1981 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Levy, Eric- Spring 88, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- Lobosco, John- ILR 498- Spring 79, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 44)
- Loiselle, Paul- Ithaca- Fall 82, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Maquart, Jules M.- Ph.D.- RR Minor, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Masiowski, Michele- Spring 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Mathis, Jeff- Florida- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- McGarry, Lynn- ILR 499- Spring 84, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- McGraw, Daniel- AL- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- McGuy, Nancy- ILR 498- Fall 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Merzer, Edith (Ag Ec) 499 (1978) (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Mendelson, Jedd- Spring 79, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Migdal, Renee H., 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Moran, Janet- Fall 79, 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Morrill, James- Spring 84- ILR 498- R.R., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Nash, Maureen (499), 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Ryan, John- ILR 499- Spring 1989 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Schaedel, Jack- Advisee- Fall 88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Brenner, Andrew- Fall 89, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Quickenton, Tamar- Fall 89, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Schade, Michael- Fall 89, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Bailey, Susan- ILR 499- Fall 88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Clark, Christine- ILR 499- Fall 88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Krazmien, Michelle- ILR 499- Fall 88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Legislative Internship, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- 499 Letters of Commendation from Legislators- 1977 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- The Legislative Process in New York State (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Adams, Laurie- Spring 83, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Bailey, Susan- ILR 499- Fall 88, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Baber, Phyllis- NYC- Fall 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Biener, Steven- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Berlin, Edward- Semester in DC- Spring 80, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Bierman, Leonard- ILR 499- Spring 75, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Bloom, Ellen- Ithaca- Fall 1982 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Bolton, Suzanne- Albany- Fall 82, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Bozzella, John- ILR 499, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Brooks, Joan W.- ILR 499, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Brossman, Mark- ILR 499- Spring 75, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Brown, Cynthia- Spring 83, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Brownstone, Robert- Spring 75- ILR 499, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Buckley, Kathleen- Fall 1980- NYC (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Burden, Elizabeth- ILR 499- Spring 79, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 37)
- Burta, David- ILR 499- Spring 75, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 38)
- Butler, Bob- Fall 86, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 39)
- Caldeira, Victoria- Washington, DC- Fall 81, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 40)
- Campanelli, Donald- ILR 499, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 41)
- Chernuchin, Cindy- ILR 499- Spring 79, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Cohen, Martin- MILR, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 43)
- Connell, Patricia- Spring 83, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 44)
- ILR 260- Student Information Sheet (Blank), 1988 (Box 24, Folder 45)
- Day, Laura (Box 25, Folder 1)
- DeAngelo, Charles, 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Debona, Elyse, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Dennis, Madeline (Box 25, Folder 4)
- De Souza, Angela, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Diamond, Tamra, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Diaz, Debra, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Diorio, Michael A., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Doherty, Glen, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Donohue, Leslie, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Doorey, Deborah- Fall 89, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Dorf, Daniel, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Dreiblatt, Dean (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Duke, Cynthia, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Eckstein, Randi- Fall 1980 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Eder, Robert, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Edlefsen, Paul Jay (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Eidelbeg, Edna (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Eilers, Susan, E., 1985 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Eisenman, Dana, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Evans, Ellen, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Ehrhart- English, Cindy L., 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Epstein, Robert, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Fabbricatore, Robert Lee, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Fairbanks, Anthony (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Falk, William, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Falke, Ellen (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Fandell, James J. (Job Candidate), 1972 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Fanning, Mark, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Farell, Shelia, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Fass, Linda Gail, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Faughn, Una, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Finn, Jody (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Feiner, Joe- ILR 368- Spring 1976, 1976-1978 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Felix, Mariel, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Fisher, Daniel (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Filipski, John C., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Flack, Jill, 1979-1984 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Flynn, Dana (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Fontana, Andrea, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Frank, Nora Ann (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Friedman, Corey, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Frito- Lay Applicants- 1987 (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Fusco, Guy, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Gabor, Marc (Labor/Management Resumes) (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Gallo, Mary, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Garrison, Paul, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Gelfond, William Jonathan (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Gilbert, Edward (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Gilmore, Ellen Pape, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Glaser, Cathy, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Glaser, Cathy- ILR 362, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Glassman, Andy- NY- Spring 82- ILR 499, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Gochman, Karen Sue, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Gray, Judd, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Green, Howard, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Greene, Jennifer C., 1983 (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Griffin, JoAnne- Spring 87, 1986-1989 (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Halpin, Jo-Anne (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Hardigan, James, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Harmon, Randy, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Hatch, William (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Hauselt, Denise, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Hayden, Donald T. (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Helfrich, Thomas G. (Box 25, Folder 65)
- ILR 260 Student Reports, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Hemmings, Madeleine B., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 67)
- Hennelly, Alyson, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 68)
- Henis, Russell- DC- Spring 81, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 69)
- Irving, Henry, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 70)
- Hessol, Nancy, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 71)
- Hickey, Kathleen (Box 25, Folder 72)
- Hirschhorn, Edward, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 73)
- Hickey, Susan, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 74)
- Hopman, Vicki, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 75)
- Horowitz, Gary, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 76)
- Hurley, Shelagh (Box 25, Folder 77)
- Hurley, Patricia, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 78)
- Hurley, Tom, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 79)
- Huttar, Tamarin (Box 25, Folder 80)
- Hymes, Lawrence, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 81)
- Izzo, Rebecca, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 82)
- Jacobs, Dan (Box 25, Folder 83)
- Jahanmir, Gina, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 84)
- Johnson, Rick, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 85)
- Johnson, Sandy (Box 25, Folder 86)
- Johnson, Teresa, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 87)
- Jones- Richter, Cheryl, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 88)
- Julian, Robert, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 89)
- Johnson, Bob, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 90)
- Kahn, Loren A. (Box 25, Folder 91)
- Kahn, David, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 92)
- Kauder, Ronnie Nan, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 93)
- Katz, Lois H.- ILR 499- Spring 79, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 94)
- Kelly, James, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 95)
- Kelly, Matthew J., 1976 (Box 25, Folder 96)
- Kendall, Nancy, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 97)
- Keogan, Christopher (Box 25, Folder 98)
- Kern, Margaret, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 99)
- Kessler, Helene Lynn, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 100)
- Kirschner, Kenneth H., 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 101)
- Klein, Joyce- NY- Spring 82- ILR 499, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 102)
- Kolbe, Stan, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 103)
- Koziar, Elaine (Box 25, Folder 104)
- Krazmien, Michelle, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 105)
- Kremer, Carole McFarland, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 106)
- Kruse, Thomas K. (Box 25, Folder 107)
- Kulka, Jeanette (Business Resume) (Box 25, Folder 108)
- Kundin, Joel, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 109)
- Kurlander, Steven, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 110)
- Kushner, Glen, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 111)
- Kushner, John, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 112)
- Kwong, Grace, 1980-1984 (Box 25, Folder 113)
- To Ori: Request for ILR Credit, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- ORI (Grade Changes/Incompletes, Inc.), 1977-1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Kaplan, Julie, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Sears, David- ILR 669 T.A. Spring 82 and Spring 83, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Dennis, Madeline- Fall 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Berman, Robert, TA (ILR 696) Fall 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Student Info Forms- ILR 260, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- ILR Advisee Forms (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Martin, Veonous- Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Sykes, Angela- Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Ferguson, Stuart Scott- Spring 90, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Manning, Ardrell- Spring 1990 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Moreno, Ruben- Spring 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Stein, Andrew- Spring 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Student Advisees for Fall 1987 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Fairbanks, Sherry Lynn, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Fink, Karen Aline, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Halpin, Jo-Anne Marie, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Johnson, Nancy Ames, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- McGouldnick, Chris (Advisee), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Park, Andrea Renee, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Quickenton, Tamar- Advisee- Fall 87, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Rink, Cheryl Lynn, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Fondacaro, Renee- Advisee 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Stinson, Valerie (Advisee) 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Thomas, Jovita- Grad Advisee, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Advisee Info, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Brucia, Catherine M., 1982 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Collins, Patty, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Donato, Cynthia A. (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Gregoire, Diane M., 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Hlawitschka, Walter 82, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Masiowski, Michele, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Nematz, Diane B., 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Otis, Clyde L., 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Poglianich, Antonio, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Reilly, Ellen, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Shinney, Janet (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Steck, Aron Wolfe, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Advisory Cums/Ori (V. Freeman), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Stewart, Andrew '81, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- DeAngelo, Charles, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Dragonette, Lisa- Fall 77, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Friskco, Gail, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Gaines, Beverly Joanne, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Galusha, Timothy, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Gardner, Wendy- Fall 77, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Glickman, Robert, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Hlawitschka, Walter, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Hughes, Debra Joan, 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Jahanmir, Gina, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- Kuranda, Patricia, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- Landgraf, Paul, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- Lavigne, Cheryl, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- Lavin, Luis, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- Lavin, Luis '81, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- Masiowski, Michele, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Morias, Paul, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Mullin, Damian, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Nematz, Diane, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- Parlett, Robert, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- Poglianich, Antonio, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Powers, Christopher, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- Prescott, William, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 64)
- Proctor, Clifford, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 65)
- Resnik, Robert A., 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 66)
- Steck, Aron, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 67)
- Silsby, Charles, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 68)
- Sinclair, Joe, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 69)
- Snyder, Tahla, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 70)
- Stewart, Andrew, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 71)